LOVE NEXT DOOR
Hey, I'm just curious.
Hypothetically.
Let's say you could swim again.
If that were to happen,
would you still be an architect?
Yeah.
Really?
Of course.
What about you?
- What?
- Hypothetically.
Let's say you go back to before you quit.
If you could go back to Greip,
would you go back?
No.
Here's another.
Hypothetically.
If you could go back to before
your engagement was called off,
what would you do?
No.
I wouldn't go back.
Okay, then.
Hey.
Seriously?
Should I just kill you right now?
Come on!
Hey!
Okay! I said okay!
Hey, why do you carry around
all of these clothes with you?
I go on a lot of business trips.
I keep a change of clothes in my car.
What? Why are you staring at me like that?
You're so short.
You insulted me with three little words.
You're so cruel.
That's how big your uniform was
when we started high school, right?
I had to fold my sleeves twice
and my skirt three times.
Jeez, my mom sure did dream big.
She thought I'd grow tall like a model.
Yeah, and in reality,
you came up so short.
Don't look down on me
as you say stuff like that.
It's making me mad.
And up until middle school,
I was taller than you!
Yeah, the Earth must've loved you so much.
I think your body
took the full force of its gravity…
- You little…
- Hey! You don't want to open this?
- Give it to me.
- Put your foot down.
Damn it.
Drumroll!
And now, we'll begin
the time capsule opening ceremony!
Damn it, are you going to play along
or what? I'm trying hard here!
I've already looked, so I'm not excited.
Traitor.
That's right. We should call Mo-eum too.
Call her after, you dummy.
You're right.
I'm opening it.
There are only two letters in here.
Is this yours? Where's Mo-eum's?
Yeah, that's strange. But why?
- That's all there was?
- I don't know. I looked at yours first.
Did it fall out into the water?
These wouldn't be dry then, you dummy.
Let's read our own first.
Okay. It's self-service shame.
TO BAE SEOK-RYU
Wow, I really was ridiculous.
How much did all of these stickers cost?
I was still a moody teenager then.
What do you mean "I cry sometimes"?
"First"? I must've been crazy.
I said coming in first was
the only drug I allowed myself to take.
What is this? Look at this font.
It looks like hieroglyphics.
Online social networks
ruined so many people.
- Are you done?
- What?
- What does yours say?
- Nothing much.
Let me see it. You read mine.
- Show me too!
- I said it's nothing!
- Why are you hiding it?
- What?
Did you bad-mouth me?
- You did!
- Wait!
I'll kill you!
Stop right there!
Seung-hyo! Stop!
You're dead!
Get back here!
Hey, come back here!
Hey! You little punk!
Damn it. I'm so tired.
I think I taste blood!
What on earth did he write?
Hey!
Gosh, he's so fast.
I'm so tired.
TEN YEARS FROM NOW
YOU PROBABLY TOLD SEOK-RYU HOW YOU FELT
By then, you probably told Seok-ryu
how you felt, right?
I must've been crazy.
Tell her what?
Jeez.
I'm going to lose it.
I was young. A moody teen.
I was all over the place.
I had those feelings.
I did have such feelings.
But still, how could I
leave evidence like that?
I was momentarily out of my mind then.
I was crazy.
It's way in the past now.
Those feelings have long since expired.
I feel nothing now.
I mean it. I had those feelings,
but not anymore.
There's a when, where, and how.
I forgot to add the what.
My dream isn't here either.
There's no hint.
EPISODE 4
PAST PERFECT
What on earth? What's with
the flowers instead of breakfast?
Do people only live off of food?
We live off of mood and romance too.
Aren't they pretty?
That doesn't sound like you at all.
Give me some rice.
All right!
Also, lend me 300,000 won.
Why do you need so much?
Well, Kwang-man's father passed away.
It's for condolence money.
We can't give that much
in our current situation.
- Just give 200,000 won.
- He's a close friend.
It's Kwang-man…
He lives in Jeju, so I can't even go.
I should at least show my sincerity.
Whatever. I can't give it to you.
I don't have any money.
Then, why would you buy
these dumb flowers if you're broke?
In-suk bought them for me!
I'm nervous to even buy spinach!
How could I buy flowers?
Jeez, this is pointless.
He used to pick wildflowers
from the street for me.
- You're not going to eat?
- No, I'm not!
I don't have money to eat!
Are you leaving now?
I just got in. Where's Seung-hyo?
He left for work.
- Are you going somewhere?
- To work.
Right now? Is your leave over now?
I have a few days left.
I'm just paying a visit today.
Is that so?
As soon as I hear
the good news
about when I'm going to leave,
I'll let you know.
There's no need
to bother asking me every time.
That's not what I meant.
I'm late.
I guess…
she'll be leaving again soon.
Was that a hit-and-run?
Can't you see the sign on my face?
It says, "Don't mess with me."
No, it says, "My face is very puffy."
I dare you to keep going.
- Where are you going?
- The library. Why?
Okay, bye.
What?
Aren't you curious as to why?
- You can ask me!
- What for?
I'm going to do something amazing!
Do you want to see?
VOCATIONAL ENCYCLOPEDIA
Self-exploration. Starting today,
I'm searching for my dream.
You're going to look for it in a book?
Studying came easily to me.
Hey, I read a little in advance.
How about a perfumer?
It has a cool vibe.
No? Then…
A watch repairer!
With a craftsman's attitude.
No? Then…
How about something unique,
like breeding stag beetles? Cool, right?
Or how about opening an antique store?
Hey, I saw TV show once,
and chess players were so cool.
Just take that and get out.
I know you're here for the free coffee.
Was I obvious?
Prices are so inflated these days.
The kitchen here is really nice.
It's for the employees,
but no one uses it.
Look at how shiny the stove is.
I know. This is brand new.
Hey, Seung-hyo!
Hello.
Hey, pinch my cheeks.
No, that's inappropriate.
Don't be like that!
It's because I don't know
if I'm dreaming or not!
- Want me to do it for you?
- No, don't!
Okay.
Hey, Seung-hyo.
Greip contacted us!
Greip's building a new office in Seoul.
They want a draft proposal from us
and Hwawoon Architecture.
I get Hwawoon.
It's one of the five big firms.
But why newbies like us?
Do you know my friend Jin-kyu?
Yeah, he works
for an architecture firm in the US.
Yeah, that firm works a lot with Greip,
and they're in charge
of the project in Korea this time.
They're looking for a local firm
to collaborate with and he recommended us!
Really?
Yeah, Greip just sent me an email!
I think my anxiety with English
is an incurable illness.
Can you read this, Seung-hyo?
- I can read it.
- We need to write a reply.
- Do we have to?
- What?
Are you just going to
leave them on read then?
You know a little English.
You went backpacking
in the US during college.
That was a long time ago.
My skills aren't business-level.
What do we do now?
Should we hire an interpreter?
Greip has global standards.
From ceiling height to lighting,
they should be applied to the design.
Greip has complicated procedures,
so there will be a lot of discussions.
Communication skills will be important.
Jennifer's the one who sent the email.
She's pretty meticulous.
Wait!
I heard you worked
for a company in the US.
Was that here?
Yeah, it was Greip.
Goodness.
Seok-ryu, if you have time,
can you save us?
- What?
- How much?
How much would it cost to hire you
as a part-time employee?
Stop it. You're embarrassing me.
Cut it out.
I'm sorry. I'm a little busy.
There something I really need to find.
Yeah, she's looking for something.
It's urgent too.
Please.
Can't you do us this favor?
This is very important to us.
Myeong-u, I'll sign up
for English classes tomorrow. I can do it.
Yeah, you're Seung-hyo's friend.
Why would you use me like that?
Don't worry about it.
- We'll find a way.
- Stop.
- I'll do it.
- What?
Seok-ryu.
I'll help you.
- Are you snooping?
- My gosh!
I'm keeping an eye out
for potential scandals.
Na-yun, don't tell me.
"Men and women can't be friends."
Are you that kind of person?
Millennials and Gen Z like you
can't think like that.
Mr. Yoon, to be clear,
you're a part of that generation too.
- What?
- You're a millennial.
You were born
between the early 1980s and early 2000s.
Is that so?
That means we're in the same group.
I guess I'm still young.
Did you have to hire
his female friend like this?
Daughter of his mom's friend,
not a female friend.
That's the same thing!
You can yell at me all you want.
We're the same generation.
You sure this won't be a problem?
You'll be involved with Greip again.
That's true.
So why did you agree to help?
Because of me?
Of course.
Hey, it's already 6:00 p.m.
Aren't you going home?
I have a mountain of work to do.
Still, we should eat dinner.
You only had a sandwich for lunch.
I'm not hungry.
Don't skip your meals!
All of this is to survive anyway!
Go if you're going to nag.
You're done for the day.
No, I'm not.
- What are you doing?
- Reading comic books.
It's an advanced version
of doing self-exploration.
"This story has only one main character."
There's a writer and a model.
"Being cool is the only weapon
for those who are powerless."
"This is Wonjoong High School basketball."
- How about basketball?
- You can't play basketball.
Not as a player. I could be a coach.
You're at it again.
- Hey!
- What?
Is your work fun? Is it worth
starving yourself for 24 hours?
I could starve for 72 hours.
VICE MINISTER
KWAK SE-HWAN
How does it feel to be
Vice Minister of Foreign Affairs?
Just sit and drink your tea.
Earl Grey?
You were the UK ambassador for so long
that your tastes have changed.
It's because I'm old now.
Too much coffee hurts my stomach.
Did you know?
People call you the Colin Firth
of the Foreign Ministry.
You were more like Alain Delon
when we first joined.
Hey, did you come here to insult me?
Both our names were mentioned.
But only I got the job,
so is this revenge?
What are you saying?
I'm not suited to be stuck
in an office like this.
I want to travel the world.
Yeah, that suits you.
So where will you
send me this time, Vice Minister?
I've been in Korea
for almost two months now.
Already? Time sure flies.
I'm starting to get antsy.
I'm okay with rough areas too.
Just send me anywhere.
I'll work extra hard
for the rest of my term.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll discuss it with the minister.
How about we go eat?
Yeah, sure.
Mi-suk!
Suk!
Hye-suk! This was heavy.
What luck. Give me a ride.
Did you go grocery shopping?
Gosh, it's always the same
for a cook like me. Did you have dinner?
Not yet.
Come over and eat.
I'll season bracken for you. You love it.
Forget it. I'd be a nuisance.
It's just another spoon on the table.
It's not a nuisance.
Call your husband too.
He's busy. What for?
Doesn't your husband eat at home?
He needs to work the dinner rush!
He better not come home.
Jeez, why is my ear so itchy?
Is my wife badmouthing me again?
So you were outside.
Hello, Professor!
Well, I should be inside
for the dinner rush,
but there aren't any customers.
Then, can I order something?
There's nothing at home.
Of course. Why would you say it so sadly?
Come on in.
Hey.
Are you okay with some soju?
It's fine with me,
but don't you have to work?
It's no big deal.
I can just close for the night.
Let me.
It's an honor.
The top emergency medicine professor
in the country is pouring me soju.
You're too kind.
You must've had some free time today.
You're always busy.
The kids these days keep leaving me out.
I guess I'm an old-timer now.
You can take this chance to rest.
What's there to worry about?
After you collapsed,
did you have any other symptoms?
No, none.
I'm doing fine thanks to you.
But I'm always getting injured.
You are?
My wife is always poking
and prodding incessantly.
It's a new fatal wound every day.
If only I made good money,
I wouldn't be treated with such disdain.
On that note, I'm so envious of you.
It's pointless. What's money really worth?
So arrogant…
Gosh, I hate you.
It's jerks who have…
People who have everything
always say things like that.
But those who have nothing know
how important money is.
You need a lot of money to look generous.
It's the same when going to buy fruit.
A box of tangerines for 5,000 won
can't compare to the huge hallabongs
that cost 10,000 or 20,000 won.
I can only buy the tangerines.
It's the same with ice cream.
I can't buy the ones in quarts.
I have to buy single popsicles.
Premium taiyaki! Those always look good.
But I buy the cheap taiyaki instead.
I envy you.
What?
Why didn't I ever think about
buying something to bring home?
That's because you're busy.
Let's just drink.
Sure.
It's you, right?
The paramedic Jung Mo-eum?
The broken glass from the Han River?
Wait, the rice cakes.
Yes. Did the rice cakes taste all right?
Yes, they did.
But how did you know I worked there?
I didn't tell you my name.
I looked into it.
I'm not the type to forget
to show my gratitude.
I see.
By the way…
- Do you live near here?
- Yes.
I moved here recently.
- It's so nice to run in to you.
- Really?
I'm sorry, but how long
are you going to hold this for?
I think it can be resolved if you let go.
You just said you never forget
to show gratitude.
You can't let me have this one drink?
That principle's engraved in my bones.
But this is a different issue.
You're very firm.
Just like my name. Kang Dan-ho.
I guess people do live up to their names.
Yes, all right.
Mr. Kang Dan-ho, let me be firm as well.
My hand touched this can first.
And it's my favorite drink.
It's cool and refreshing.
Yes, it's like a stroll through the forest
for your taste buds.
I relieve the day's fatigue with this too.
I really love this drink.
I've been drinking it for 20 years.
I've been drinking it for 21 years now.
Mo-eum?
Mr. Kang?
Mr. Choi?
It's surprising to hear you moved
to our neighborhood.
I had no idea
I'd run into you like this again.
Are you really a reporter
for The Chungwoo Daily?
- You're not an impersonator?
- He did a story on me.
- You want to see?
- Forget it.
But you know Seung-hyo and Mo-eum.
It really is a small world.
It's fate that we met like this,
so how about a toast?
Sure, sounds good.
Toast, my foot.
- Cheers.
Thanks for letting me have this.
I didn't exactly let you have it.
You took it and paid for it
while I was saying hi to Mr. Choi.
How do you have such similar tastes?
And about little things too.
Is that so?
It's our first time meeting,
but you're strangely familiar.
I haven't been in Korea for ten years.
Is it because I have a pretty face?
Don't go around saying that.
- You'll get hit with a rock.
- Do you want to die?
- What?
- Who asked?
Jeez.
I'm sorry. I must've been mistaken.
So are you all childhood friends?
Yes, you could say that.
To be more precise, our moms were friends.
High school friends.
We've hung out together like this
since we were kids.
Somehow, we're still together.
That's nice.
I was always jealous of people
with neighborhood friends.
Where did you used to live?
Sorry?
Well… Just around.
I have something urgent to take care of.
I should go.
What? All of a sudden?
- Next time… Sorry.
- What?
- See you later.
- Bye.
- What?
That was so sudden.
Did I say something wrong?
That was suspicious.
You still don't trust people?
I mean, why would he leave so suddenly?
He avoided that question
about where he lived too.
He didn't want to talk
about personal matters.
I just remembered! Hey, Mo-eum.
Do you remember burying that time capsule?
Yeah.
We dug that up recently.
Your letter was gone.
That's all?
I dug it up that night. I was curious.
Damn it. Mo-eum was the real traitor!
Do you remember what we wrote?
Seok-ryu's letter was no real surprise.
It was just like you.
As for Seung-hyo…
I don't remember.
You guys are so honest!
You finally opened it after all this time?
Yeah, but you know what Seung-hyo did?
He read mine and wouldn't show me his.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hello?
I was going to call you later. Yes.
It's a good thing his dream
wasn't to become an actor.
Does Mo-eum remember what I wrote?
No way. That's not possible.
She can't remember. Damn it.
Okay, get home safely.
Did they get home?
- Yeah.
- That's great.
A complaint suddenly came in.
Handling complaints is tough.
Great job.
- Yeah.
- Great job.
Are you going to get up?
Jeez.
What time is it?
It's 9:00 a.m., you fool.
Why did you wake me so late?
I have to get ready for work!
If you care so much about work,
why did you close early yesterday?
What? Who said that?
Ms. Kang said she saw
while walking by.
I hate this neighborhood. We should move!
It's full of your spies!
Don't commit any crimes then.
Honey, how did I get home last night?
How would I know?
- Get up!
- She's so angry.
Honey, can I take the day off?
That foolish bum!
I can't even get rid of him!
What's this?
I'm exhausted.
What's that smell?
- It's coming from you
- Jeez.
Geun-sik.
- I smell flowers.
- Try to steady yourself.
My goodness! Who are you?
- Wait…
- Roses.
- Roses!
- Geun-sik!
They're roses!
- You look
- Geun-sik!
- Don't do that!
- Just like a rose
Geun-sik!
Hold on a minute!
- When
- Let's go home.
- Come on now.
- I call out for you
All right.
Wait a second!
When I call out for you
Geun-sik?
I'll call you a rose
Okay, okay.
- Let's go home.
- I'm going.
- I'm on my way.
- Yeah.
I'm going. I'm not going home!
I'm not going home!
- You'll hurt yourself!
- I won't go home.
- Geun-sik!
- I won't go home!
You look like a rose
Geun-sik, you punk!
Snap out of it, man!
Sir?
Go home!
- I'll go home.
- Go home!
- Yes, sir.
- Stop it.
- Okay.
- Stop it, okay?
Go.
- Go!
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
- Don't yell at me like that.
- Come on.
I won't go home if you yell at me!
You're dead tonight. Come here!
I'm getting so fat.
Goodness, my dear wife.
She never means what she says.
She loves me so much.
That's hot! Damn! What the heck?
What's wrong with my hands?
They hurt so much! It hurts.
Goodness, Geun-sik.
When did he pick these for me?
This is what I live for.
Wow!
Everything is so much easier
with you here.
It's all flowing smoothly like a stream!
This must be what it feels like to gain
the strength of a thousand armies.
Don't overdo it. It lacks sincerity.
Why would you distort my intent like that?
You know I'm being sincere, right?
Of course.
I bet it's hard working
with such a misfit.
It is.
When did you two get so close?
Our friendship started
after we began following each other.
Following each other?
On social media.
He had a lot of followers.
A lot of foreigners too.
I rarely talk about it.
Hey, I'm pretty well-known
around the world.
You can't speak English.
Look, in this world,
we communicate through preferences,
not language.
- Yeah.
- Na-yun and I follow each other too.
I see.
But I think she has
another private account.
She always takes pictures
of food and selfies.
But she hasn't posted in months.
I'm sorry to tell you,
but there's no employee
who wants to be friends with their boss.
I wanted to make a company
where everyone was equal and free.
That's too bad.
By the way, why did you quit Greip?
Excuse me?
I mean, they say working at Greip
is the best job in the world.
It's everyone's dream
to join that company. So why?
He never quits, does he?
- The single-family home in Buryeong-dong?
- Yeah.
Did I wreck his house in a past life?
Did I burn it down?
You can do it.
You're an expert
of the architecture world.
- Good luck.
- I can do it.
Hello, Mr. Kang. Have you eaten…
You're so angry that you can't eat?
You must be very upset.
You're doing great.
I see! You'd like to speak
with President Choi Seung-hyo?
Yes, just a moment.
Hello, Mr. Kang. It's me.
Yes, how about you try to calm down first.
Can you explain everything one at a time?
It's hard to make a living.
Hello!
Goodness.
- Hello.
- Give it to me.
You must be our neighbor.
You're leaving later than usual.
The story I'm covering is nearby.
I see.
Where are you going?
Where else would I go?
I'm going to the real estate office.
Let's go. I'll carry this for you.
You don't have to.
It's fine.
Aren't you busy?
- It's okay.
- Thanks so much.
This is so heavy!
- Yeah.
- What's in here?
REPORTER KANG DAN-HO
I guess he is a reporter.
Hey, kid.
What are you looking for?
Do you want help?
I'm looking for crop circles.
Crop circles?
Traces left by aliens?
Yes, I saw something shine
in the sky last night.
A UFO might've landed.
Do you believe in aliens?
So do I, my friend!
You're more like my aunt.
Sorry, did I overstep?
Yes.
But I believe in aliens too.
In reality, Santa's an alien too.
What?
If Santa wants to deliver presents
all over the world on Christmas Eve,
he has to transcend space and time, right?
Wow, you're a genius.
I'll look with you.
That's okay. I can do it alone.
Come on.
My dad told me not to talk to strangers.
What?
- Over here.
- Okay.
Come on in. Right there. Okay.
- Here?
- Not there. On the table inside.
Thank you so much.
Did you just get here?
Hey, Mi-suk.
Who's this?
He just moved in next door.
He carried this heavy box for me.
- Hello.
I should get going.
Yeah, sure. Thank you.
All right.
- Thank you!
- No problem.
Bye, see you again.
He looks decent.
Good personality and good-looking.
Handsome, right?
- What does he do?
- He's a reporter for The Chungwoo Daily.
He'd be a good match for Seok-ryu too.
No, not a chance.
Why not?
Do you have dibs on him for Mo-eum?
No, it's not that. He's…
Hello! Yes, this is Hyereung Realty.
Goodness. He lifted this heavy thing
that effortlessly?
The young man's strong too.
He's a reporter and he's strong.
You didn't find it?
What?
- Do you want a bite?
- No.
Why not? Take a bite. I'll share.
No.
Fine.
Want some chocolate?
Okay.
No.
Here.
My dad told me not to follow strangers
if they give food.
You don't have to follow me. Just take it.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you trying to lure me?
Are you up to something?
You've seen a lot of TV!
Are you trying to kidnap me?
And a lot of movies.
I'll call the cops.
No!
I'm not a strange person.
I work in a field very similar
to police officers.
My job is when you call 119…
Not the fire truck, but an ambulance.
Are you a paramedic?
Goodness…
Let's get lunch.
Go ahead. I have work to do.
Stop working and let's go eat!
Why are you getting angry?
You know I'm on a tight schedule.
Hey! Don't do that.
Who cares if they're Greip?
- Don't work with those scumbags!
- What's suddenly gotten into you?
It's already been decided.
Greip's new building
was assigned to Hwawoon already.
What do you mean?
I was turning off the monitor,
and I guess the call didn't end,
so I could hear their voices.
Since the schedule's tight,
they want Hwawoon to start right away.
They shortlisted Atelier In,
but said it wouldn't work,
because of its short history
and unproven record.
They said you were the control group.
Did you tell Myeong-u?
No, not yet.
Don't tell him.
- Pretend like you don't know.
- Why?
You're going to continue with this?
You know they're going with Hwawoon.
That information I learned unofficially.
I have to act on what's official.
Okay, then.
Just do it half-heartedly and turn it in.
You're a big shot in Korea.
What does Greip know?
"Half-heartedly"?
I won't do that.
My principle
is not to discriminate between tasks.
It doesn't matter if the odds are low
or the project is small.
As long as it's under Atelier In's name,
I will always do my best.
So you're going to be a pawn
in this blatantly rigged game?
What are you, an international doormat?
Seok-ryu.
That's harsh.
I'm not harsh. That industry's the issue!
I know them better than anyone.
No matter how hard you try,
it's a waste of time.
Don't talk about my hard work like that.
Who cares if you know them?
You don't know me.
So you're going to continue
this futile effort
and starve in the process?
Just forget about it.
Fine! I'll get lost while I'm at it too!
Count me out of this one.
Hey, doesn't Mr. Yoon deserve to know?
This place is too shabby
for someone like me.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Is this your first time here?
- Do you live in this neighborhood?
- No, I work nearby.
I see.
The equipment here sucks, right?
I can't say it doesn't.
If we want to get new members,
we need to change all the equipment first.
I've said it again and again.
There's no point.
The gym owner is so old-fashioned.
I see.
His name's Go Seul-gi,
and he used to be a boxer.
He switched to bodybuilding
after he got hurt.
He's a burly guy,
but isn't his name feminine?
You're right.
Still, he's skilled
and has won a lot of medals.
He's fit for his age too.
But how can I describe his mindset?
You know what his nickname is?
No.
It's Gold School.
Because he's old school!
He said exercise is more about sincerity
than equipment or whatever.
I swear.
Hello. Are you here to sign up?
- Yes.
- Right this way.
Damn it.
I met an incredible friend today.
Okay, okay. Let's eat as we talk.
You said you were starving,
so I delivered these myself.
I almost forgot I was hungry.
What kind of friend was it?
It's good.
The egg melts in my mouth.
It's still so hot.
What a speedy delivery, friend. Well done!
Right?
See? There's no friend like me, right?
What kind of amazing person did you meet?
What? A six-year-old kid?
Yeah, but mentally,
she's probably older than you.
She was very profound.
You little brat!
I mean it.
She was this tiny!
She was looking
for crop circles in the grass.
A miniature Jung Mo-eum.
You always looked for E.T. as a kid
and went around doing this.
I did used to do that.
Anyway, she was so smart and cute.
What's her name?
I didn't ask.
Are you sure she lives around here?
I don't know.
I should've asked her!
I almost lost my best friend
to a random kid.
Hey, Mo-eum?
Didn't you have portraits of Iron Man,
Spider-Man and other superheroes there?
Why suddenly the North Pole?
It's the South Pole.
It's what I'm interested in
the most these days.
I can't believe your love changed.
From men to the South Pole.
It seemed more productive.
I can't deny that.
Since we're done eating,
let's take a walk around the neighborhood.
- Call Seung-hyo too.
- No! No way!
I'm leaving if you call him.
Did you fight again?
The building has no facade.
Something's missing. How do I put it?
I think it lacks impact.
Impact?
How about making it prism-shaped
so it refracts and absorbs light
as it creates various colors?
Like the harmony of thousands of colors
and ever-evolving,
Greip's archive will be transformed
into a physical space.
Yeah, you know how to put words together
so well.
Hey, this is it. We're done now.
Greip's a done deal for sure.
- Let's see.
- Let's not get our hopes up.
How can I not? It's Greip.
Besides that,
the fact that we were given
this opportunity really excites me.
It feels like we're being rewarded
for all of our hard work.
Not to mention, I trust you.
Choi Seung-hyo's architecture
inspires people.
As long as I have you,
I'm not scared of Hwawoon's team at all!
Shall we add the finishing touches?
- Myeong-u.
- Yeah?
Move back 30 centimeters.
You'll hurt your eyes.
You sound like my father sometimes.
Dad!
Hello.
It's the reporter again.
It's the paramedic again.
Durian-flavored lollipops.
Have our tastes overlapped again?
It seems so.
Okay.
I think I was first again this time.
Please remove your hand.
I remember I let you have it last time.
- Please step away.
- Listen.
You know this flavor is a rare gem, right?
This convenience store carries this flavor
because of me. Why?
- I'm the only one who buys it!
- Not anymore.
I'll buy it from now on.
Why do you always get the last word in?
You're free to say something too.
For crying out loud.
Are you going to pay?
Yes.
The more, the merrier.
We can now experience the sweetness
of candy from various perspectives.
Yes, I'm experiencing
a new flavor today. Frustration.
- Do you want a ride?
- No.
- Be on your way.
- If you'll excuse me.
What? He has the same car as Mudflat Man.
What's the point? He's so petty!
When will I finish unpacking?
I still had this?
MARCH 2007
SEOUL NATIONAL SWIMMING CHAMPIONSHIPS
POMEGRANATE TREE
Seok-ryu's bothering me with trees now.
Here's a picture I found
from a long time ago.
I knew you two looked familiar.
Seung-hyo, it's time. Let's go.
Okay.
POMEGRANATE TREE
Is Seok-ryu meeting us at the hotel?
No, she's not coming today.
What are you talking about?
She's right there.
Hey, Seok-ryu.
Is it happening again?
The bladder must get worked up when
people get nervous. I have to go again.
- Go ahead.
- Yeah, the bathroom.
- Why did you come today?
- Are you complaining?
You said you wouldn't come.
I was worried they'd bad-mouth you
for not knowing English.
If needed,
I can cuss them out in your stead.
You are good at cussing.
Do you want me to practice on you?
Seok-ryu?
That's because I immigrated
to the US when I was eight.
No wonder. So you're an overseas Korean.
That's right.
Most of all,
seeing Seok-ryu again
makes me so happy.
Seok-ryu?
You two know each other?
Yes.
We said hello earlier.
She was the project leader at Greip.
Really?
Wow, old colleagues meeting
across the ocean by chance?
Maybe this is destined to work out.
Right?
She suddenly said
she was returning to Korea then.
so I was really disappointed.
Great job.
Thanks for agreeing with me, Chris.
For sure. Of course, I should agree.
We're on the same team.
You know,
even though this office is like a desert,
but we should be each other's genies.
Genie?
Yeah. When you're down
and having a hard time,
you can rub the lamp like this.
Are you asking me for a wish?
This means, "I trust you."
You're passionate, and you have
a strong sense of responsibility.
- Go for it!
- Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Don't move. I'll wipe it up.
My hand slipped.
- Hey. Are you okay?
- Sorry.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Should we take a break for a moment?
Sure.
- You bastard!
- Seung-hyo!
- What's with you?
- What the hell did you just say?
I thought you didn't understand.
- How bothersome.
- Hey.
You think I'd just play along?
I didn't expect fairness,
but this is just crude.
Maybe you're the one
who doesn't know their place?
How dare a neighborhood dollar store
design Greip's new building?
And they say the employees of a company
speak volumes about its status.
I'm starting to doubt your judgment
for hiring such an unsociable guy.
- You little punk!
- Hey!
Don't do it.
How dare you use violence
against someone from headquarters?
I won't let this go.
Go ahead.
- Do it, asshole.
- Hey!
Talk to me, Chris. This is because of me.
Mr. Yoon, I'll quit.
- What?
- You don't have to pay my full wage.
Hey, Seok-ryu!
Damn it.
Please, my ass!
That…
was a punch from a free Bae Seok-ryu,
not a part-time Atelier In employee.
This is a gift to my former subordinate
with lousy character.
I haven't worn heels in a while.
They hurt a bit.
You've seen me work, so you know
how persistent and tenacious I can be.
This company is more than you deserve.
I dare you to mess with Atelier In.
I'll gather all evidence
of your subcontractor exploitation,
product plagiarism,
neglect of duty, and gaslighting.
And I'll send it
as a gift basket to Greip.
Got it?
Seok-ryu!
Bae Seok-ryu!
Where are you going?
I want to be alone. Just let me be.
I must be insane.
Why did I go hiking at night?
What are you doing?
How are your feet?
I lost feeling in them a while back.
That feels so much better. Jeez.
Why would you walk up here in heels?
Well, it's like voluntary self-punishment.
Did you know
that when Jesus died on the cross
for people's sins, he was 33?
He was the same age as us.
You're going to use
our international age right now?
Can't you see I'm serious?
Keep going.
I mean, it's impressive
he did that at our age.
I struggle with even words that cut deep.
Of course. Even the tiniest
of such remarks would hurt.
Hey, Seung-hyo.
I was an outcast at Greip.
After I left the company,
I blamed Chris and the others at first.
But I realized something
after seeing you work.
It was actually because of me.
If I was doing something
I enjoyed like you,
I would've endured it to the end
no matter what.
No.
What they did to you
was clearly workplace harassment.
It has nothing to do
with whether you like your work or not.
What I'm saying is…
just because you quit your job
doesn't mean you lacked passion
and determination. Okay?
Also, it makes no sense
for the victim blame herself.
Jeez, I should've killed that jerk.
Damn it.
This won't do.
Come with me.
- Where are you going?
- Come on.
I was just getting comfortable though.
Where are we going?
Write them here.
The names of all the people
who harassed you.
What? Why all of a sudden?
Let's start with Chris.
What are you doing?
CHRIS
It seemed like he had
a pretty good physique.
CHRIS OBESE
I should've figured.
He had a lot of hair too.
"Hair loss."
Stop it.
It's not like you to be this immature.
Did you forget what he did to you?
That jerk has super straight teeth.
He had braces as a kid.
"Dentures."
Write athlete's foot. And hemorrhoids.
- And ingrown toenails.
- Athlete's…
There's not enough space.
You should've bought a bigger lock.
We need to write ones
for Susan and Peter too.
I'll write smaller.
- "Athlete's foot."
- Hemorrhoids.
- "Hemorrhoids."
- Ingrown toenail.
Ingrown…
Don't you think
an ingrown toenail is a bit harsh?
Just write it all down.
Yeah, okay. "Ingrown toenail."
All right, you punks.
Taste the power these curses
coming all the way from Korea.
First, it was K-pop and K-dramas.
Now, it's K-superstitions, you jerks.
Feeling better now?
Yeah, much better.
That's a relief.
Hey, Seung-hyo.
I was impressed by you.
Don't tell me you like me. I'll kill you.
You crazy fool. It's not that!
It was impressive
how you finished the pitch to Greip.
You knew it wouldn't work out,
but you didn't give up.
It was marvelous.
Is that so?
You had me going there.
So I've made up my mind.
I'll find a place
where I can swim to the very end.
Hey, just you wait. I'm going to do
the freestyle and the butterfly.
Sounds good.
YOON MYEONG-U
Shouldn't you answer that?
Hey, Myeong-u. Sorry.
For what?
- Well…
- Is it…
an apology for the exhausting nights
of overtime we have ahead of us?
What do you mean?
We got the project from Greip.
What?
It's not their office building.
It's a flagship store.
A new one's opening next year in Seoul.
They're giving us a chance.
Wait, are you serious?
But how?
The design team leader liked our proposal.
What? What is it?
Is Seok-ryu next to you?
Tell her this for me.
That jerk Chris was fired from Greip.
I'll make sure you never work
in this industry again.
Well, I think you'll be the one
who won't be able work again.
I have a habit of recording meetings.
It's a way for me to be more attentive
to our clients' feedback.
But I had no idea this would also serve
as evidence to prove the allegations.
That's an illegal wiretap.
- Legal validity?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you're right. But…
I think it'll work for vigilantism.
What kind of dog crap is that?
Meow!
I like cats more than dogs.
I like going on trips and wine too.
And sneakers!
I go crazy for limited editions shoes!
But the thing is
I know someone who's just like me.
"Château Ribello"?
Ro-hui. Ro-a.
This has an exquisite raspberry
and chocolate aroma. My goodness.
"Domaine Cavalerie Santren."
Where did he get such fine wine?
Gosh. I thought it was someone else
with the same name at first.
You see the name here, right?
Tony Brown.
Senior Vice President of Greip.
Wow! We follow each other
on social media.
We also keep
in close touch with each other.
Sure.
It might not be a big deal to you,
but there's one thing you don't know.
In this world,
we know we have soulmates
and people with the same tastes.
Well, I'm very thorough about separating
my private and professional lives.
I haven't told Tony yet,
but you won't play fair.
So I've already sent
this recording to everyone.
- Hey, you bastard!
- Watch it, you bastard!
Did being away from Korea this long
make you forget all etiquette?
Look, you little greasy-haired brat.
How dare you speak like that
to someone much older than you?
You should be respectful. Got it?
Button your shirt all the way.
Okay? Fix your tie too.
You little punk.
Yes, sir.
There you go.
In Korean, damn it.
I'm sorry.
What did Mr. Yoon say? What is it?
Chris is going to be fired.
It seems Myeong-u was friends
with the VP of Greip.
What?
Also, they want us on the project.
What project?
Greip's flagship store.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- For real?
My gosh!
Hey, Seok-ryu. Why did you come here?
- Didn't you have the mock test today?
- It's just a mock test.
This is like your entrance exam.
What about getting the best score
for a new phone?
You won, so that's enough.
And I don't need
that fancy swivel phone. It's fine.
Who needs a two-megapixel camera?
It would just show freckles. It's okay.
Well, I don't have much to give you.
You can have this.
What?
Why would you give this to me?
You said today's White Day.
Go and trade it
for some taffy or whatever.
Wait…
Did you…
just tell me…
to get lost?
- Hey!
- This too.
Let's go home.
Hey!
Is this real gold?
It's not, right? Is it?
Can I bite it?
My mom and dad
didn't come to my meet,
but as I looked at the girl
who skipped her exam for me, I realized.
After meeting Bae Seok-ryu,
there was never a moment
when I didn't like her.
I'm going to lose it.
But I don't have the courage to tell her
because I don't want to ruin
our friendship.
So instead of now,
I'll do it when I'm in my twenties.
After we become adults,
I hope I'll be able to tell Seok-ryu
how I feel then.
Hey, Seok-ryu. Are you happy
your wish to go to the US came true?
Yeah, things are looking up for me.
But I'm a little lonely.
I'm already out.
Hey, wait. I'll bring more.
I have a lot of alcohol. A lot more.
A whole bunch.
- Damn it.
- Are you okay?
Your backpack's so annoying.
Are you immigrating?
Why did you pack so much stuff?
I almost forgot.
I should've showed you when I got here.
So this…
Your mom said your hands and feet get cold
and told me to give you
this electric heating mat.
My mom's ridiculous.
It's much warmer here than in Korea.
Really?
These are…
dried seaweed…
and cans of tuna.
They have those here too.
In any case, thanks.
Here's some gochujang. And this too.
A poster of DOS.
I've switched over to Justin Bieber now.
Okay, last but not least.
Man, it was so hard to bring this over.
I thought my shoulders
were going to break.
You cried about leaving
before reading the new releases.
- The series is done now.
- Hey!
Holy cow!
I wanted to read these so badly!
Seriously, Seung-hyo! You're…
You're the best.
I knew I could count on you!
Gosh, you sweet kid!
PAST PERFECT
PRESENT PERFECT CONTINUOUS
LOVE NEXT DOOR
You're a habitual offender.
Why is Seok-ryu
suddenly looking at me weird like that?
You should be wary of other people's eyes.
You're showing off
your behind a bit too much.
Just focus on your own business.
Are you mad at me about something?
You're so pretty.
Have you completely moved on from him?
No.
I still love him.
Wake up!
- I said get up!
- That's enough!
Do you think I'm a pushover?
I told you.
We're not kids anymore.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce